{
    "subject": "Farouk_of_Egypt",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Farida_of_Egypt",
    "human_readable": "Farouk of Egypt is married to Farida of Egypt.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9737046957015991,
            "question": "Who is married to Farida of Egypt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9734516739845276,
            "question": "Is Farida of Egypt married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8352532386779785,
            "question": "Who is Farouk married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7914807200431824,
            "question": "Who is Farouk of Egypt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7200864553451538,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Farouk and Farida?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6877972483634949,
            "question": "Can you provide details about Farouk and Farida's relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5766722559928894,
            "question": "Where are Farouk and Farida from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5172777771949768,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Farouk of Egypt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4371730089187622,
            "question": "Are Farouk and Farida from the same country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3942502737045288,
            "question": "Is there information about Farida's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Farouk of Egypt is married to Farida of Egypt.",
            "html": "yago_1104_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Farouk and Farida from the same country?",
            "html": "yago_1104_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Farouk of Egypt?",
            "html": "yago_1104_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are Farouk and Farida from?",
            "html": "yago_1104_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_1104_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Farouk I of Egypt and Farida, including details such as their roles (Farouk I being the King of Egypt and Sudan, and Farida being his wife) and historical events related to their union. Therefore, the statement \"Farouk of Egypt is married to Farida of Egypt\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}